Guide to the Mark Bloch Postal Art Network (PAN) Archive MSS.170
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Mail Art and Correspondence, 1976-2009; 22.5 Linear Feet in 44 manuscript boxes, 8 box binders, and 6 oversize flat boxes.
  - United States (Texas), 1983-2005 (Box 80, Folder 4-9, Box 84, Folder 2, Box 86, Folder 1,6, Box 87, Folder 1, Binder 15, Binder 17, Box 88, Box 90, Box 94, Folder 23-25, Box 98, Box 99)
    Correspondents include: Al Ackerman, Angela Genusa, Art Cellar Gallery, Bill Shields, Gene Wesley Elder (Mud Underground), GFC, IAO, John Held Jr., L'Art Postal Futuriste, La Muerte, MAKA Super Science, MANO, Marg Dixon, Maureen O'Malley, Modern Realism Gallery, O!! ZONE, R.N. Manning, Saphire Phoenix, WALL-TET.
  - United States (Vermont), 1985-1995 (Box 81, Folder 1-2, Binder 15, Binder 16, Box 88, Box 90, Box 99)
    Correspondents include: Chester Kasnowski, Jesse Dreibelbis, Johnny B, Karen Kraham, The Handsome Johnson Mail Art Grant Token, The LDFS.
  - United States (Virginia), 1983-1986 (Box 81, Folder 3-4, Box 83, Folder 2, Box 86, Folder 7-8, Binder 15, Box 88, Box 89, Box 98, Box 99)
    Correspondents include: Dav DeT Hompson, Edgar Allen Bushmiller, Gail Pink (A.KA. Neo-girl), Gene Laughter (SOS), Jeff Bagato, Mark Dechagas, Robert Saunders, Rubber Moon Stamps.
  - United States (Washington), 1981-2000 (Box 81, Folder 5-9, Box 82, Folder 1, Box 83, Folder 2,7, Box 84, Folder 6, Box 85, Folder 4, Box 86, Box 87, Folder 1,2,4, Binder 16, Binder 17, Box 89, Box 90, Box 92, Folder 8, Box 93, Folder 9, Box 97, Box 99)
    Correspondents include: Artinform, Brice Roosevelt, Deena Manis, Deena Manis and Talbot Uehlinger (Long Life Candles), Dinosour Mayonaise, John Bennett, Kay Marie Pobunz, Larry Huber "Esquire", Liz Gasper, Penumbra Journal, Robert Ashworth, Shack, Simonson, The National Mobilization for Justice and Peace, Tim Scanelli.
  - United States (Washington DC), 1984-1995 (Box 82, Folder 2-3, Box 87, Folder 1,4, Box 98)
    Correspondents include: Chris Keeley, Michael Voo Doo, National Archives and Record Administration, R.A.M.A, The American University: School of Communication, United States Senate (Daniel Patrick Moynihan), Wendy Lanxner.
  - United States (West Virginia), 1986-2004 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    Correspondents include: Charles Roberts, Ficus strangulensis, resident lark, Valhalla of Cowpars, J. Michael Mollohan, sean whatever.
  - United States (Wisconsin), 1984-1993 (Box 82, Folder 5, Box 87, Folder 1, Binder 17, Box 103, Folder 13)
    Correspondents include: Circle, Edna Carlsten Gallery, Patrick Beilman, Resident Chicken, Xexorial Endarchy.
  - United States (Wyoming), 1990-1992 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    Correspondents include: Jane H. Fonfara, Nielsen Gavine.
  - United States (U.S. Military), 1993 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    Correspondents include: Tom Kudla
  - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1989-2001 (Box 82, Folder 9, Box 87, Folder 1, Box 99, Box 104, Folder 14)
    Correspondents include: Aleksander Badyukov, Anatoly Zhigalov, Eugene Shaskin, Joe Willie Nameth, Jonas Nekrasius, Peter and Angela Kustermann, Vladimir Sutagin.
  - Uruguay, 1984-1992 (Box 82, Folder 10-11, Box 86, Folder 5,8, Box 87, Folder 4, Box 98, Box 105, Folder 1)
    Correspondents include: Clemente Padin, Eduardo Acosta Bentos, Osmar Santos.
  - Venezuela, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 12, Box 105, Folder 2)
    Correspondents include: CO(REO) ARTE
  - Wales, 1985-1989 (Box 82, Folder 13)
    Correspondents include: Alice-Rainbow, Barry Edgar Pilcher.
  - Yugoslavia, 1984-1988 (Box 83, Folder 1, Box 88, Box 90, Box 99, Box 105, Folder 3)
    Correspondents include: Andrej Tis̄ma, Bálint Szombathy, Jaroslav Supek, Nenad Bogdanović, Nevenko Petrić.
- Series II: Non-Mail Art Periodicals, Announcements and Flyers, 1980-2007
  This series consists of periodicals, announcements, flyers, catalogs and other mailed material collected by Mark Bloch over four decades.
  This series has been arranged alphabetically by category.
  - # [Art Flyers], 1983-1993 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - 124 Ridge Street Gallery, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - 479 Gallery, 1985-1997 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - 494 Gallery, 1992-1995 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - A [Art Flyers], 1985-2002 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - A [Art Flyers], 1984-1999 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - [Art: ABC No Rio], 1985-2007 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - [AIDS], 1985-1988 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Alternative Museum, 1986-1995 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - American Fine Arts Co., 1993-2004 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Anthology Film Archives, 1989-2002 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Artforum, 1989-1992 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Art Workshop, 1990-1994 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Artists Space, 1984-1993 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Artsits Talk on Art, 1986-1990 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Asian CineVision Inc., 1984-1990 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - B [Art Flyers], 1980-1997 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Bang on a Can, 1989-1998 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - [Tanya] Bonakdar/Gallery Jancour, 1995-1999 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - [Books: Publishing & Literary Events], 1985-2003 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - [Books: Publishing & Literary Events], 1984-1993 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - [Books: Publishing & Literary Events], 1985-2004 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - [Books: Publishing & Literary Events], 1984-2003 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - [Books: Publishing & Literary Events], 1987-1997 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Bound & Unbound, 1990-2004 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Brooklyn Academy of Music, 1989-1998 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - C [Art Flyers], 1985-1998 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Carnegie Hall, 1997-2005 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - CB's 313 Gallery / CBGB, 1990-1992 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Center for Book Arts, 1985-2003 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Chelsea Art Museum, 2005-2007 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - The City University of New York: The Graduate Center, 2002-2005 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Claire Dunphy's Studio, 1984-1990 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Cleveland Performance Art Festival, 1990-1997 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Cohen Gallery, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Community and Politics, 1985-1993 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Community and Politics, 1987-1992 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Community and Politics, 1987-1992 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Community Education Center, 1989-1996 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - The Cooper Union, 1993-2007 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Creation Star Trek Convention, 1990-2005 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Creative Time, 1989-2000 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - D [Art Flyers], 1993-2000 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - [Dance], 1984-2005 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Deep Dish TV Network, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Dick Shea, 1992-1998 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Dixon Place, 1993-2004 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - E - F [Art Flyers], 1986-2005 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - [Education], 1985-2006 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - [Education], 1985-2002 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - [Education], 1986-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Emily Harvey Gallery, 1987-2002 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Exit Art, 1994-2001 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Experimental Intermedia Foundation (Phill Niblock), 1987-1992 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - FEZ - Under Time Cafe, 1993-1996 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Film Forum, 1998-2001 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Film/Video Arts, 1994-2000 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - [Film], 1984-2004 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - [Film], 1985-2004 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Francis M. Naumann Fine Art LLC, 2004-2007 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Frank Maya, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Franklin Furnace, 1983-1992 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - G [Art Flyers], 1983-2003 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Generous Miracles Gallery, 1999-2001 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Gracie Mansion Gallery, 1985-2000 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - H - I [Art Flyers], 1985-2005 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Harvestworks, 1990-2000 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Himalayan Institue of New York, 1987-1992 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - J [Art Flyers], 1984-1997 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Japan Society, 1993-2006 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - LABAN/BARTENIEFF Institute of Movement Studies, 1986-1990 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - K [Art Flyers], 1980-1996 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Kenny Schachter conTEMPorary, 1986-2007 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Kent State University, 1986-2003 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Kent State University, 1985-2007 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Kent State University, 1985-2007 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Kent State University, 1985-2004 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Kent State University, 1988-2006 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Kent State University, 1988-2007 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Kent State University, 1984-2002 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Kim Foster Gallery, 1996-2006 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - The Kitchen, 1989-2003 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - The Knitting Factory, 1994-2002 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - The Knitting Factory, 1988-2001 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - The Knitting Factory, 1988-2001 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - L [Art Flyers], 1984-2007 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - La Mama La Galleria, 1988-2006 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Libertarian Book Club, 1985-1995 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Limelight, 1986-1988 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Lincoln Center Theater, 1993-2002 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Lower East Side Tenement Museum, 1990-1998 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Lyons Wier Gallery, 2004-2007 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - M [Art Flyers], 1984-2006 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - M [Art Flyers], 1985-2006 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Manhattan Neighborhood Network (MNN), 1994-2001 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Manhattan Neighborhood Network (MNN), 1994-2000 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Manhattan Neighborhood Network (MNN), 1994-2000 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Manhattan Neighborhood Network (MNN), 2001-2005 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Merkin Theater, 1991-2007 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Miller Theater, 2001-2006 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Monroe Community College, 1987-1998 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Museum of Modern Art, PS 1, 1987-2005 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - [Music Flyers], 1992-2004 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - [Music Flyers], 1987-2006 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - [Music Flyers], 1987-2006 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - [Music Flyers], 1986-2006 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - [Music Flyers], 1989-1999 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - [Music Flyers], 1989-2000 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - [Musical Theater, Opera], 1984-2007 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - N [Art Flyers], 1984-2006 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - New England Art Therapy Institute, 1988-1998 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - The New School, 1994-2006 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - The New York Open Center, 1986; 2004 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - The New York Public Library, 1989-2004 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - New York University, 1986-2006 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - No Business As Usual Action Network, 1986-1990 (Box 28, Folder 2, Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Nuyorican Poets Cafe, 1990-1992 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - O - P [Art Flyers], 1984-2007 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - The Painted Bride, 1988-1996 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Paper Tiger Television, 1992-1998 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Pavel Zoybok Gallery, 2005-2007 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Piezo Electric, 1984-1985 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - [Poetry - Publication & Performance], 1984-2004 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Printed Matter, 1986-2006 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Printed Matter, 1990-2004 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Printed Matter, 1991-1998 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - PRIX ARS Electronica - International Competition for CyberArts, 1994-2005 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - PS 122, 1990-2000 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - PS 122, 1989-2004 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Public Art Fund, 1985-1991 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Public Art Fund, 1987-1992 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Puffin Foundation, 1994-1998 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Q - R [Art Flyers], 1984-2006 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - S [Art Flyers], 1984-2002 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - See Hear, 1993-1998 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Silverstein Gallery, 1995-1997 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - The Sound Art Foundation, Inc., 1993-2005 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - The Sound Art Foundation, Inc., 1996-2007 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - The Sound Art Foundation, Inc., 1993-2004 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Stephen Gang Gallery, 1997-2001 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - [Subscriptions], 1984-2001 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - [Subscriptions], 1984-2001 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Surf Reality, 1993-1997 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Synagogue Space, undated (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - T [Art Flyers], 1985-2006 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - [Technology], 1986-1996 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - [Television], 1984-2004 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - [Theater - Performance], 1991-2004 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - [Theater], 1986-2003 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - [Theater], 1994-2004 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Thread Waxing Space, 1991-2004 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Thread Waxing Space, 1993-1999 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - The Time Is Always Now, 1995-2002 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Tracy Williams, Ltd., 2006-2007 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - T2 Art & Co, 1993-1995 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - U - Z [Art Flyers], 1985-1998 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - University of Buffalo State University of New York, 1993-2004 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - USPS [United States Postal Service], 1984-2000 (Box 30, Folder 9, Box 105, Folder 7)
  - WCSB 89.3 Cleveland State University, 1987-1992 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - White Columns, 1987-2007 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1990-2001 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - World Music Institute, 1990-2004 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - World Wide Video Festival, 1990-1995 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Series III: Objects, 1979-1995
  This series contains objects that were mailed to Mark Bloch as part of the Mail Art Network.
  This series is arranged by object size.
  - "If You're PAN, I'm Mickey Mouse!" Hand Painted Mickey Mouse Ornament by Mike Boals [Brooklyn, NY and Cleveland, OH], 1986 (Box 67, Object ID: 170.2.0001)
  - Green Box with Object Assemblage by DP Robert [Jackson Heights, NY], January 28, 1984 (Box 68, Object ID: 170.2.0002)
  - "Shroud of Brian": Submission for Last Mail Art Show, Small White Box from BC [Indianapolis, IN], July 8, 1983 (Box 60, Object ID: 170.2.0003)
  - "At the Shrine of the Red Spot" White Box with Red Candle, February 13, 1984 (Box 60, Object ID: 170.2.0004)
  - Swiss Breakfast Box Assemblage, July 27, 1987 (Box 57, Object ID: 170.2.0005)
  - Secured Brown Jewelry Box, November 3, 1988 (Box 68, Object ID: 170.2.0006)
  - Empty Cardboard Tube from S. Random [Greenfield, MA], March 27, 1984 (Box 40, Object ID: 170.2.0007)
  - Empty Cardboard Tube from Jaromir Svozilik [Falun, Sweden], December 12, 1983 (Box 38, Object ID: 170.2.0008)
  - Empty Cardboard Tube from LEVEL: Submission for Last Mail Art Show [Indianapolis, IN: 1 of 2], June 2, 1983 (Box 38, Object ID: 170.2.0009)
  - Empty Cardboard Tube from LEVEL: Submission for Last Mail Art Show [Indianapolis, IN: 2 of 2], July 18, 1983 (Box 38, Object ID: 170.2.0010)
  - "Important Mail" Cardboard Box from Deena K. Manis [Olympia, WA], December 26, 1982-January 23, 1983 (Box 63, Object ID: 170.2.0011)
  - Wrapped Gerber Box from Deena K. Manis [Olympia, WA], January 19, [1983] (Box 64, Object ID: 170.2.0012)
  - "Very Truly Yours" Sculpture from Tsai-lang Huang [Tampa, FL], November 17, 1984 (Box 60, Object ID: 170.2.0013)
  - Sunglasses from Miss Louise [East Northpoint, NY], February 6, 1986 (Box 68, Object ID: 170.2.0014)
  - Small Bag of Brick by Mark Bloch, undated (Box 68, Object ID: 170.2.0015)
  - Empty Cardboard Tube from Met Desion [NY, NY], July 9, 1990 (Box 40, Object ID: 170.2.0016)
  - Sponge Picture Postcard, undated (Box 60, Object ID: 170.2.0017)
  - Comb and Sunglasses Assemblage by Hermine Stover / Muscles Duchamp / Endangered Species [Tustin, CA], July 25, 1984 (Box 64, Object ID: 170.2.0018)
  - "Yes I Can Be Cruel If You Like" Green Paper Assemblage [Endangered Species - Tustin, CA], undated (Box 57, Object ID: 170.2.0019)
  - "Wounded, Cowardly Soap Fragment" in Twin Pan Alley Doblado Cigar Box from Your Mind / Endangered Species [Tustin, CA], July 17, 1984 (Box 62, Object ID: 170.2.0020)
  - "Hand in Hand" Paper Sculpture by Seiko Miyazaki [Osaka, Japan], December 1988 (Box 66, Object ID: 170.2.0021)
  - Small Metallic Ornament by Blind and Insane [Endangered Species - Tustin, CA], July 28, 1984 (Box 68, Object ID: 170.2.0022)
  - Decorated Jolly Time Plastic Container from Winged Tootsie [Endangered Species - Tustin, CA], July 6, 1984 (Box 58, Object ID: 170.2.0023)
  - "Make One Again" Artwork by Owen F. Smith, undated (Box 57, Object ID: 170.2.0024)
  - Gold Leaf Book in Small E. Nobel Tobacco Box by Hot Jets Herm / Endangered Species [Tustin, CA], July 26, 1984 (Box 62, Object ID: 170.2.0025)
  - Styrofoam Sculpture by Kim [Akron, OH], March 26, 1979 (Box 59, Object ID: 170.2.0026)
  - "I, too, find it increasingly hard to be mysterious, but I can make a terrific exit" Photograph with Wooden Block from Endangered Species [Tustin, CA], June 25, 1984 (Box 62, Object ID: 170.2.0027)
  - Wrapped Gumbo Graphics Box from The Great Mail Art Supply [Greenport, NY], 1983 (Box 68, Object ID: 170.2.0028)
  - Schimmelpennick Tin from Hermes / Endangered Species [Tustin, CA], June 30, 1984 (Box 68, Object ID: 170.2.0029)
  - Small Largo Cigar Box from Her Mind's Images / Endangered Species [Tustin, CA], July 26, 1984 (Box 65, Object ID: 170.2.0030)
  - Empty Cardboard Tube from Jordi Solé Disseny: Submission for UN / One World Postal Art Show [Tarragona, Spain], September 22, 1995 (Box 40, Object ID: 170.2.0031)
  - Empty Cardboard Tube from Hermine / Endangered Species [Tustin, CA], August 1984 (Box 40, Object ID: 170.2.0032)
  - "Don't Be An Angel" Wrapped Styrofoam Box from S. Random [Greenfield, MA], March 12, 1985 (Box 60, Object ID: 170.2.0033)
  - Friedel Confiserie Box Wrapped in Brown Paper Bag, November 17, 1983 (Box 62, Object ID: 170.2.0034)
  - "Absolutely No Fabulous Feminine Fragrances What Ever" from H., undated (Box 58, Object ID: 170.2.0035)
  - Hot Jetfire Model Airplane Wing, undated (Box 64, Object ID: 170.2.0037)
  - Small Gray Jewelry Box with Correspondence on Red Paper from HCP West / Endangered Species [Tustin, CA], June 28, 1984 (Box 62, Object ID: 170.2.0038)
  - "Facts About Las Venus, 'Play Planet of the Gods,' " Handmade Polaroid Book by Son of Zeus & Maia (female form) / Endangered Species / Hermine Stover [Tustin, CA], July 6 [no year] (Box 64, Object ID: 170.2.0039)
  - Yellow Flor de Tabacos Tin from Endangered Species [Tustin, CA], July 6, 1984 (Box 57, Object iD: 170.2.0040)
  - Potato Pancake Mix Box from Endangered Species [Tustin, CA], July 26, 1984 (Box 61, Object ID: 170.2.0041)
  - Decorated Cigar Box from Divine Messenger Service, Inc. / Endangered Species / Hermine Stover [Tustin, CA], July 26, 1984 (Box 61, Object ID: 170.2.0042)
  - "Portrait of a Deserted City" from Hermine Stover / Endangered Species [Tustin, CA], July 28, 1984 (Box 68, Object ID: 170.2.0043)
  - Ciba Consumer Pharmaceuticals Box from Hermine Stover / Endangered Species [Tustin, CA], 1984 (Box 68, Object ID: 170.2.0044)
  - "Formerly" Living Plants Plastic Packaging from Endangered Species / Hermine Stover [Tustin, CA], July 27, 1984 (Box 65, Object ID: 170.2.0045)
  - Fisher-Price Teethers & Rattles from Louisey [Miss Louise - East Northpoint, NY], January 21, 1986 (Box 66, Object ID: 170.2.0046)
  - Empty Priority Mail Box from Lipman [Mill Valley, CA], February 4, 1994 (Box 65, Object ID: 170.2.0047)
  - Empty Cardboard Box from Endangered Species / Hermine Stover [Tustin, CA], July 11, 1984 (Box 38, Object ID: 170.2.0048)
  - Empty Decorated Cardboard Box from God 'n Us Productions [Springfield, MA], January 30, 1984 (Box 40, Object ID: 170.2.0049)
  - "Name Dropping Game" from Steve Random [Greenfield, MA], undated (Box 60, Object ID: 170.2.0050)
  - Painted Styrofoam Assemblage in Red Talisman Box, undated (Box 41, Object ID: 170.2.0051)
  - Leather Wallet and Pen Assemblage from Dr. Klaus Groh: Submission for Last Mail Art Show [Augustfehn, Germany], December 14, 1983 (Box 61, Object ID: 170.2.0052)
  - Handmade Cermaic Candle Holder from Larry Rippel [Pittsburgh, PA], December 10, 1983 (Box 58, Object ID: 170.2.0053)
  - "Who Loves You?" Handmade Book by Contemporary Realism / Bob Crise [Columbus, OH], April 23, 1984 (Box 61, Object ID: 170.2.0054)
  - Sculpture by Massimo Pattaro [Torino, Italy], May 22, 1989 (Box 39, Object ID: 170.2.0055)
- Series IV: Serials, 1972-2007
  This series contains serials (magazines, zines, newspapers, catalogs, and newsletters) that Mark Bloch collected between 1978 and 2013. Strengths of this series include documentation of the small magazine culture from the downtown scene in the last decades of the twentieth century, including a zine written by Donna Tartt.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by serial title.
  - 11x30 [vol. 2 no. 1; vol. 3 no. 1], 1989; 1990 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - 11x30 [vol. 4. no. 2], 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - 10003 [vol. 1 no. 4, 5], 2004-2005 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - 1 XS [vol. 2 no. 9], 1984 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - @-WIRE [vol. 1 no. 9], June 1-15, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - ABCD Catalog, undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Abe Adler 100 Years, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Advantage, Winter 1993 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Aerial Print, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Aerosol #21, January 21, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - After Image [vol. 21 no. 4], November 1993 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Ah Pook Is Here #6, undated (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Ah! L'Arte Postale #7536, June 1989 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Ajax Catalog 14, April-August 1992 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Alex Glidzen Postcard Memoirs (1-100), December 1990 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - American Express [unnumbered; vol. 3 no. 2], 1992; Spring 1994 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Angry Thoreauan #13, May 1995 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Anthology Film Archives Catalog, 2004; 2006 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Archive Photos/Archive Films Calendar, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Are You Drunk?, October 1955 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - The Arrow: Bulletin of the Mackay Society, Fall 1986 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Art + Communication Network #1, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - The Art Economist [vol. 2 no. 11], September 30, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Art Issues #29, September-October 1993 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Art Monthly #200, October 1986 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Art Now Gallery Guide, December 1991; Summer 2000; April 2002 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Art on Paper [vol. 4 no. 1], September-October 1999 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Art Police, 1987-1993 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Art Police, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - ARTtalk [vol. 11 no. 11], September 2001 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Art Unidentified, 1985-1995 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Arte Postal!, March-April 1995 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Artefact, undated (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - At Zip's Pop Top Tavern, undated (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Austad's Breakthrough!, Spring 1992 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Barbie Doll Bitches from Hell by Robert W. Howington & Paula Weinman, undated (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Battle Cry Sounding [#128; #129], 1995 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Beat Happening [#8; #10; #11], undated (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Bela Lugosi's Magazine Issue 3: Horror, undated (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Bern Potter, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Between the Lines, 1987; 1996 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Bikini Girl, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Bile, undated (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Bill Dipp Soho Detective: The Dress My Father Died In, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Bizarre, April 2001 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Black Eye [#9; #10], undated; Winter 1980-1981 (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - Body Bulletin, July 1985 (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - Book Source Monthly [vol. 17 no. 2], May 2001 (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - Bottom Line [vol. 12 no. 19, 20, 21, 23; vol. 13. no. 6], 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - Brain in the Mail, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - Brigadista Bulletin #13, February 1985 (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Bright Trash Zine, Winter-Spring 1989 (Box 42, Folder 52)
  - Burning Press '91, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 53)
  - Business Week, March 7, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 54)
  - Catalogue of Exhibitions in Show Your Colors, October 28-December 29, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 55)
  - Celebrate with the Bar/Bat Mitzvah Guide, December 31, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 56)
  - Chaotic Art, June 1995 (Box 42, Folder 57)
  - The Characteristics of Mental Illness, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 58)